[{"answer": " my friend told me she met him at the beach. Got blinded by his smile.  You believe that shit?  Son of a bitch never smiled at me.  Buried her at a", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He came in with my friend to the restaurant where I work.  That's not where they met", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Hang about.  I thought you said he come into the restaurant where you worked with my friend", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "And that's where you met my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'm so glad we're having this chat", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's not a compliment", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's not what I heard", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I heard you were", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Not embarrassed", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Not ashamed", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, I reckoned, Saturday night, if you were goin' out, you'd probably have to come home first", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, saw my friend, yeah.  Me and him are muckers", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Nah, accommodation address", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Something like that, yeah", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "-- Your employer", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Who's Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What'd you want me to do.  Stay at home, twiddlin' me thumbs.  Doing sweet F.A. ", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What do you think", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Told you you wouldn't be able to see through that gate", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Who'd you butcher at the house", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What I like about my friend, he believes in a chain of command, but not a chain of respect, you understand what I'm saying", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah.  I really admire the guy.  Well. Good to meet you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why didn't you just kill him, you had the chance", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Too easy", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "As it happens.  I didn't make that part up", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know everyone here.  He was so traumatized he split.  Maybe he was my friend's ", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The forever kind", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Get seven years, did you", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Just now?  Overnight", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "So what", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "And I said so what.  You think she's any happier", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "But I can't be sure.  I don't even know who he is.  He's too insulated.  Too many layers around him", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Yeah, I guess you are", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "All of what", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Oh, yeah, right.  The deal", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " In which case I'll just do what I usually do", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What am I doing", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "So you wouldn't have any idea how your client continues to make so much fucking money", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Where is he now", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You've made it ... brighter", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Sure you do", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "the-limey.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Tell you ..", "qsentId": 44}]